Usage: @capgo/cli bundle upload|u [options] [appId]

Γ¼å∩╕Å Upload a new app bundle to Capgo Cloud for distribution.

Version must be > 0.0.0 and unique. Deleted versions cannot be reused for
security.

External option: Store only a URL link (useful for apps >200MB or privacy
requirements).
Capgo never inspects external content. Add encryption for trustless security.

Example: npx @capgo/cli@latest bundle upload com.example.app --path ./dist
--channel production

Options:
  -a, --apikey <apikey>                     API key to link to your account
  -p, --path <path>                         Path of the folder to upload, if not provided it will use the webDir set in capacitor.config
  -c, --channel <channel>                   Channel to link to
  -e, --external <url>                      Link to external URL instead of upload to Capgo Cloud
  --iv-session-key <key>                    Set the IV and session key for bundle URL external
  --s3-region <region>                      Region for your S3 bucket
  --s3-apikey <apikey>                      API key for your S3 endpoint
  --s3-apisecret <apisecret>                API secret for your S3 endpoint
  --s3-endpoint <s3Endpoint>                URL of S3 endpoint
  --s3-bucket-name <bucketName>             Name for your AWS S3 bucket
  --s3-port <port>                          Port for your S3 endpoint
  --no-s3-ssl                               Disable SSL for S3 upload
  --key-v2 <key>                            Custom path for private signing key (v2 system)
  --key-data-v2  <keyDataV2>                Private signing key (v2 system)
  --bundle-url                              Prints bundle URL into stdout
  --no-key                                  Ignore signing key and send clear update
  --no-code-check                           Ignore checking if notifyAppReady() is called in source code and index present in root folder
  --display-iv-session                      Show in the console the IV and session key used to encrypt the update
  -b, --bundle <bundle>                     Bundle version number of the bundle to upload
  --link <link>                             Link to external resource (e.g. GitHub release)
  --comment <comment>                       Comment about this version, could be a release note, a commit hash, a commit message, etc.
  --min-update-version <minUpdateVersion>   Minimal version required to update to this version. Used only if the disable auto update is set to metadata in channel
  --auto-min-update-version                 Set the min update version based on native packages
  --ignore-metadata-check                   Ignores the metadata (node_modules) check when uploading
  --ignore-checksum-check                   Ignores the checksum check when uploading
  --force-crc32-checksum                    Force CRC32 checksum for upload (override auto-detection)
  --timeout <timeout>                       Timeout for the upload process in seconds
  --multipart                               [DEPRECATED] Use --tus instead. Uses multipart protocol for S3 uploads
  --zip                                     Upload the bundle using zip to Capgo cloud (legacy)
  --tus                                     Upload the bundle using TUS to Capgo cloud
  --tus-chunk-size <tusChunkSize>           Chunk size in bytes for TUS resumable uploads (default: auto)
  --partial                                 [DEPRECATED] Use --delta instead. Upload incremental updates
  --partial-only                            [DEPRECATED] Use --delta-only instead. Upload only incremental updates, skip full bundle
  --delta                                   Upload delta updates (only changed files) for instant, super fast updates instead of big zip downloads
  --delta-only                              Upload only delta updates without full bundle for maximum speed (useful for large apps)
  --no-delta                                Disable delta updates even if Direct Update is enabled
  --encrypted-checksum <encryptedChecksum>  An encrypted checksum (signature). Used only when uploading an external bundle.
  --auto-set-bundle                         Set the bundle in capacitor.config.json
  --dry-upload                              Dry upload the bundle process, mean it will not upload the files but add the row in database (Used by Capgo for internal testing)
  --package-json <packageJson>              Paths to package.json files for monorepos (comma-separated)
  --node-modules <nodeModules>              Paths to node_modules directories for monorepos (comma-separated)
  --encrypt-partial                         Encrypt delta update files (auto-enabled for updater > 6.14.4)
  --delete-linked-bundle-on-upload          Locates the currently linked bundle in the channel you are trying to upload to, and deletes it
  --no-brotli-patterns <patterns>           Files to exclude from Brotli compression (comma-separated globs, e.g., "*.jpg,*.png")
  --disable-brotli                          Completely disable brotli compression even if updater version supports it
  --version-exists-ok                       Exit successfully if bundle version already exists, useful for CI/CD workflows with monorepos
  --self-assign                             Allow devices to auto-join this channel (updates channel setting)
  --supa-host <supaHost>                    Custom Supabase host URL (for self-hosting or Capgo development)
  --supa-anon <supaAnon>                    Custom Supabase anon key (for self-hosting)
  --verbose                                 Enable verbose output with detailed logging
  -h, --help                                display help for command
